investorshangout.com 2016-06-27

# Privacy Policy | Investors Hangout

Your use of the Investors Hangout Website indicates to us that you have read and accepted our privacy practices, as outlined in this Privacy Policy 

**Aggregated Information**

Aggregated information is collected through various methods. For example, we collect IP addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers, the computers that "serve up" Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address, and when you request a page from a Web site, its servers log your IP address. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, so although your session will be logged, you will remain anonymous to the site. We collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration. 

**Use of Cookies**

Our site also uses "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that most major Web sites write into your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies allow a Web site to measure activity on their site and to improve your user experience – for example, by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences, thus allowing you to visit various member-only parts of the site without re-registering. We do not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. Except for personal information voluntarily provided by you (i.e., during registration), we do not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes, and that information is not shared with third parties. 

You may occasionally get cookies from advertisers on the site, which is standard on the Internet. These cookies are outside the control of our site, and are not subject to our privacy policy. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of the site, such as the member-only areas, will not function properly if you do so. 

**Links to Other Sites**

It is important to note that this site contains links to other sites, and that those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as our site. For instance, if you click on an advertisement on the site, this will take you away from the site and to an entirely different site. These sites may send their own cookies to you, and may collect data and make uses of it that this site would not. 

**Commitment To Children's Privacy Protection**

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, no information should be submitted to or posted on the message board by users under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 are not eligible to use our services 

**  
Security**

We take every precaution to protect our users' information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. If you think someone has your password, you should immediately access your account and change your password. Investors Hangout takes steps to secure the data you submit to us, including storing all critical user data and limiting the number of people who have physical access to our user data. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, Investors Hangout cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you understand that you do so at your own risk and we will not be held responsible.]. In addition, please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you may disclose publicly in any chat rooms, forums, message boards, or similar web pages. You should keep in mind that whenever you publicly disclose information about yourself online via message boards or chat rooms, that information could be collected and used by people that you do not know. 

**Use and Disclosure of Collected Information**

Investors Hangout does not rent, sell or otherwise disclose your personal information to third parties unless disclosed to you at the time such information is collected or unless you otherwise give consent, other than in the following limited circumstances: 

Legal action. Investors Hangout may disclose information about its users, including personal information, when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our website and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website. Investors Hangout may also disclose user information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability, to protect or defend our rights or property or protect the safety, rights or property of our users. 

**Email**

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Website, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at the link provided in the newsletter. 

**Privacy Policy Modification.**

Investors Hangout reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice, so please review this policy from time to time for changes and updates. 

**Contacting Us  
**   
If you have any questions regarding this policy, if you would like us to remove the information that you have provided us, or if you have any other concerns regarding your online privacy, we encourage you to contact us by simply sending us an email. We welcome your questions and concerns.
